/* eslint-disable no-unused-vars */
const QUESTIONS = {'200': [{
  'id': 1,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '$200',
  'question': 'Which property is used to change the font color of an element',
  'answer': 'color'
},
{
  'id': 6,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '$200',
  'question': 'The elements that need to be put inside of a form are input, button and',
  'answer': 'label'
},
{
  'id': 11,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '$200',
  'question': 'Everything in JavaScript is an object',
  'answer': 'false'
},
{
  'id': 16,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '$200',
  'question': 'Git automatically adds new files to the repository',
  'answer': 'false'
}],
'400':
[{
  'id': 2,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '$400',
  'question': 'Which property is used to change the font size of an element”',
  'answer': 'font-size'
},
{
  'id': 7,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '$400',
  'question': 'What tag defines a cell in a table',
  'answer': '<td></td>'
},
{
  'id': 12,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '$400',
  'question': 'Local storage data is stored in',
  'answer': 'file system'
},
{
  'id': 17,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '$400',
  'question': 'What command is used to create to a new branch called name',
  'answer': 'git checkout -b name'
}
], '600':
[{
  'id': 3,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '$600',
  'question': 'The outermost component of the CSS “box-method',
  'answer': 'margin'
},
{
  'id': 8,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '$600',
  'question': 'What element creates a form',
  'answer': '<form></form>'
},
{
  'id': 13,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '$600',
  'question': 'JavaScript is a case-sensitive language',
  'answer': 'true'
},
{
  'id': 18,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '$600',
  'question': 'The following command will add all changes to be staged for commit',
  'answer': 'git add .'
}
], '800':
[{
  'id': 4,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '$800',
  'question': 'If no positioning is set in a CSS element, what is the default positioning',
  'answer': 'static'
},
{
  'id': 9,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '$800',
  'question': 'The <img> requires a closing </img> to be valid',
  'answer': 'false'
},
{
  'id': 14,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '$800',
  'question': 'A function __________ loads before any code is executed',
  'answer': 'declaration'
},
{
  'id': 19,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '$800',
  'question': 'What are the three steps to get changes from the local machine to github',
  'answer': 'add commit push'
}
], '1000':
[{
  'id': 5,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '$1000',
  'question': 'What is the primary difference between grid and flexbox',
  'answer': 'grid is 2 dimensional & flexbox is 1 dimensional'
},
{
  'id': 10,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '$1000',
  'question': 'Which best describes the <canvas> element',
  'answer': 'container for graphics'
},
{
  'id': 15,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '$1000',
  'question': 'A function ______ loads only when the interpreter reaches that line of code',
  'answer': 'expression'
},
{
  'id': 20,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '$1000',
  'question': 'To download a Git repository named \'repo\' on your local machine for the first time which Git command would you use',
  'answer': 'git clone https:github.com/repo'
}
]};
